managewp.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy - ManageWP

Our sites use cookies and other tracking technologies to let us know how you interact with our services, to enrich your experience and the relevance of our advertising. This tool allows you to out out of such tracking. Note that blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience on our websites and the services we are able to offer. 

Essential Website Cookies

These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with essential services and functionality, including identity verification, service continuity and site security. Opt-Out is not available. 

Marketing Cookies

Make sure we do not repeat the same advertising messages, that the messages are more relevant to you and your interests, and allow us to measure our advertising effectiveness. 

Analytics Cookies

These cookies collect anonymous data on how visitors use our site and how it performs. We use these to improve our products, services and user experience. 

Support Cookies

These cookies are used to track user activity and failed actions, so we could have more data when we start troubleshoot your issues. Powers interactive services such as chat support and customer feedback tools. 

#### OVERVIEW

ManageWP (“Company” or “we”) is serious about protecting your privacy.  We appreciate your trust and will strive to do so carefully and sensibly.  This notice (this “Privacy Policy”) describes how we may collect personal information from the visitors to our site, how we may use it, with whom we may share it, what choices you have regarding it, and how we protect it.  This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is a part of the [ **Terms of Use**](http://managewp.com/terms-of-service) of this Company Web site ( managewp.com, this “Site”) and we encourage you to become familiar with the terms and conditions contained herein.

#### CONSENT

**By accessing and using this Site, you agree that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy, and that you accept and consent to the Company’s privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

#### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our [ **Terms of Use**](http://managewp.com/terms-of-service) at any time.  The Company may change its privacy practices because of changes in relevant and applicable legal or regulatory requirements, the business or business practices of the Company, or in its attempts to better serve your needs.  Notice of such changes to our privacy practices will be given in the manner described in the Company’s [ **Terms of Use**](http://managewp.com/terms-of-service) for this Site and a revised Privacy Policy will be posted on this Site.

#### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT **?**

The Company may collect various types of information from or about you depending on how you use the Site and its various features.  In particular, during the Site registration process and the ManageWP subscriber registration process, you supply us various types of information, including personal information that you choose to disclose, and information regarding how you use the Site, which we collect as you interact with our Site.

With respect to personal information, you may provide us with various types of information.  Such information may include you and your company’s name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, transaction information, as well as billing and payment information that you voluntarily provide to the Site.  This information is generally entered into fields in the registration and subscription forms and enables you to take full advantage of the products and services that we offer.  Should you purchase or use any Company products or services on or through the Site, the information that you supplied during the registration process may be used to track details about those purchases or use.  We may collect email addresses from customers and visitors to the Site for the purpose of communicating with customers.  If at any time you wish to be removed from the Company’s email database, you can request removal by contacting [helpdesk@managewp.com](mailto:helpdesk@managewp.com).  We reserve the right to contact you via postal mail, email or telephone strictly for the purpose of administering your account. ****

The Company may also retain the content of and metadata regarding any correspondence you may have with the Company or its customer service representatives, regardless of the mode of communication by which such correspondence was made.  This includes, without limitation, real time shipping information, specific container information, and any other information contained and consented to, as described in the [ **Terms of Use**](http://managewp.com/terms-of-service). This information helps the Company to improve the Site and the materials, products and services that we offer on the Site, and to more effectively and efficiently respond to both current and future inquiries.

As with many other Web sites, the Web servers used to operate the Company Site collect certain data pertaining to you and the equipment and communication methods that you use to access the Internet and the Site.  Without combining these data with other sources of information, they do not readily identify you.  They do reveal such things as the Internet protocol (“IP”) address assigned to your computer, pages you accessed on the Site, or immediately prior to visiting the Site, and the length of time you accessed the Site.

This information is collected to, among other things, facilitate Site operation and system administration, to generate aggregate, non-identifiable statistical information, and to improve content and content delivery with regard to the Site and the materials, products and services that the Company makes available on the Site.

## **Cookies and Tracking Technologies**

Cookies and similar technologies on our websites and our mobile applications allow us to track your browsing behavior, links clicked, items purchased, your device type, and to collect various data, including analytics, about how you use and interact with our Services. This allows us to provide you with more relevant product offerings, a better experience on our sites and mobile applications, and to collect, analyze and improve the performance of our Services. We may also collect your location (IP address) so that we can personalize our Services.

When you visit or interact with our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, we or our authorized service providers may use cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies to make your experience better, faster and safer, for advertising purposes and to allow us to continuously improve our sites, services, applications and tools.

We hope the information below provides you with clear and comprehensive information about the technologies we use and the purposes for which we use them, but it you have any additional questions, or require any additional information, please contact us at privacy@godaddy.com.

### Your consent

By continuing to use and navigate our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, you are agreeing to our use of cookies, web beacons and similar technologies as described herein our Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to accept these technologies in connection with your visit to or use of our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, you may visit our Privacy Settings and see additional options below available to you to manage, control and opt out of use of these technologies.    

### What types of cookies, web beacons and similar technologies do we use and why 

Our cookies, web beacons and similar technologies serve various purposes, but are generally either necessary or essential to the functioning of our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, help us improve the performance of or provide you extra functionality of the same, or help us to serve relevant and targeted advertisements.  More specifically:

**Strictly Necessary or Essential:** ‘Strictly necessary’ or “essential” cookies, web beacons and similar technologies let you move around the website and use essential features like secure areas and payment information. Without these technologies, services you have asked for cannot be provided. Please note that these technologies do not gather any information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you’ve been on the internet. Accepting these technologies is a condition of using our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, so if you prevent these from loading we can’t guarantee your use or how the security therein will perform during your visit.

**Performance:**  ‘Performance’ cookies, web beacons and similar technologies collect information about how you use our website e.g. which pages you visit, and if you experience any errors. These cookies do not collect any information that could identify you and is only used to help us improve how our website works, understand what interests our users and measure how effective our content is by providing anonymous statistics and data regarding how our website is used.  Accepting these technologies is a condition of using our sites, services, applications, tools or messaging, so if you prevent these from loading we can’t guarantee your use or how the security therein will perform during your visit.

**Functionality:** These cookies, web beacons or similar technologies are used to provide services or to remember settings to improve your visit.

**Advertising:** First or third-party cookies and web beacons may be placed by our sites, applications, or tools, in order to deliver content, including product related advertisements, relevant to your specific interests on our sites or third-party sites. These technologies allow us to understand how useful our advertisements are, and improve the relevancy of the content delivered to our users.

We also utilize 3rd party service providers to assist us in delivering on the same functions, which means that our authorized service providers may also place cookies, web beacons and similar technologies on your device via our services (third party cookies). They may also collect information that helps them identify your device, such as IP-address, or other unique or device identifiers.

### How to manage, control and delete cookies, web beacons and similar technologies 

You may manage certain cookies, web beacons and similar technologies we place by either choosing the Cookie Settings option upon first visit to our website or by visiting our Privacy Settings tab on our Setting page. 

You may block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon as you visit our site. Please note, as further described in our Privacy Policy, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a “ _Do Not Track_ ” signal from a visitor’s browser.

Internet browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings are usually found in the ‘options’ or ‘preferences’ menu of your internet browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful. Otherwise you should use the ‘Help’ option in your internet browser for more details.

If you wish to withdraw your consent at any time, you will need to delete your cookies using your internet browser settings. 

#### More information about cookies 

Useful information about cookies, including information about deleting or blocking cookies, can be found at: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

A guide to behavioral advertising and online privacy has been produced by the internet advertising industry which can be found at: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

Information on the ICC (UK) UK cookie guide can be found on the ICC website section: [http://www.international-chamber.co.uk/our-expertise/digitaleconomy](http://www.international-chamber.co.uk/our-expertise/digitaleconomy)

## Gathering Personally-Identifying Information

Once you register with ManageWP and sign in to the Service, you are not anonymous to ManageWP.

When registering with ManageWP, you provide Personal Data, which may include company name, industry, number of employees, phone number, your title, city, state, country, zip code, a user name, confirmed email address, and a password. When backing data up with the Service, you send us that data and you also are sending file system information, including names of files and directories. ManageWP may also record your IP address when you submit information.

ManageWP also may collect, at your option, certain preference and demographic information from you.

#### HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT?

In addition to the uses mentioned or described above, the Company uses the information that it collects from or about you to improve the materials, products and services that the Company makes available on the Site, to notify you of changes made to the Site or new products or services made available on or through the Site, to evaluate your needs and customize Site content delivered to you according to those needs, to facilitate the processing of any purchases or uses you make through the Site, to send you promotional material from the Company and some of our affiliates, and for other legitimate and lawful business purposes of the Company.  Other than to the extent necessary or convenient for the Company to perform the [Terms of Use](http://managewp.com/terms-of-service), the Company does not share information collected about you with third parties, except with regard to certain special programs that we offer in connection with some of our business affiliates, which may involve special promotions and/or pricing, and in which you are participating.  Should you register as a participant in one of those programs, the Company will acknowledge your registration and notify our applicable business affiliate of your registration, thereby enabling you to receive the corresponding program benefits.  At this time, which may be subject to change in our sole discretion, it is our policy not to sell lists containing personal information about Site users, registrants or subscribers.

All information collected by ManageWP is used for internal purposes of providing the Service, providing support to users, and to improve services. Aggregating non-identifying information supplied by users allows ManageWP to understand its user base and to improve services.

To protect your account information, please keep your password secure.

#### WE DO NOT COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN

Children under 13 years old are not the target audience for the Site.  To protect their privacy, we prohibit the solicitation of personal information from these children.  If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit your email address or any other personal information to us through the Site.

ManageWP does not intentionally gather Personal Data about visitors who are under the age of 13.

## Anonymous Information

We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you. We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information at our discretion.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

ManageWP discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on ManageWP’s behalf or to provide services available at ManageWP’s website.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using ManageWP’s service, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. ManageWP will  **not rent or sell  **potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, ManageWP discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when ManageWP believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ManageWP, third parties or the public at large.

#### DISCLOSURE FOR LEGAL PURPOSES

We reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable information or other information we collect through the Site or otherwise if we are required to do so by law or if we reasonably believe that the disclosure is necessary in order to (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform to the requirements of law or to comply with legal process served on us; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property or third party licensors of any material on the Site; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health or safety of the users of the Site or the general public.

Your use of the Site, including any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our [ **Terms of Use**](http://managewp.com/terms-of-service) and all dispute resolution provisions therein, limitation on damages and choice of law.  We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.  Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

## Changes and Deletion of Your Data

You may change some but not all of Your Personal Information in Your account by editing Your profile within Your account. You may contact ManageWP at any time at [helpdesk@managewp.com](mailto:helpdesk@managewp.com) if You would like ManageWP to delete Your account and any associated data (other than Anonymous Information).

#### HOW DO WE PROTECT INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU?

The Company places a high value on protecting information transmitted via this Site.  For this reason, we use state-of-the-art security solutions to process payments and to provide secure communication methods.  In addition, the Site is protected by a firewall that provides a high level of security.  The Company takes commercially reasonable measures to secure and protect customer-specific information transmitted via or stored on our Site.  However, no security system is impenetrable.  We cannot guarantee that information users supply to us will be totally secure.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. [Click for more information about the security of our technology](http://managewp.com/how-managewp-handles-security).

#### BUSINESS TRANSFERS

As the Company continues to grow and develop its business, it is possible that its corporate structure might change or that it might merge or otherwise combine with, or that substantially all of its assets might be acquired by, another company.  In any such transactions, customer information generally is, will most probably be, and should be expected to be one of the transferred business assets.

#### LINKED SITES

For your convenience, some hyperlinks may be posted on the Site that link to other websites not under the control of the Company.  Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to our Site and not to other websites of other organizations to which we link.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any other third party sites.  You should make your own inquiries regarding them.  In addition, when you initiate a transaction on a website that our Site links to, even if you reached that site through our Site, the information that you submit to complete that transaction becomes subject to the privacy practices of the owner of that linked site.  You should read their privacy policies to understand how they use and protect personal information that they collect.  The Company is not responsible for the privacy or information practices of its suppliers or any third party websites.

#### GOOGLE DATA

Should you choose to connect your Google account, it will have the following effect: Your Google Analytics data will be displayed on your ManageWP dashboard and in the client reports. It will not be stored on our end. Your Google Drive will be used as a repo to store your website backups, plugins and themes. You will also be able to restore your website from Google Drive, as well as install plugins and themes from it. Your email can be used to send client reports to your clients. Your emails will not be accessed, stored, and no other type of email will be sent by ManageWP. No Google data of any kind will be shared with 3rd parties.

#### WHAT CHOICES DO YOU HAVE?

You may update at any time the information about you and your personal preferences stored on the Site derived from your registration on the same.  You may also ask us at any time to remove your name from our list of Site users who wish to receive electronic communications and e-mail advertisements from the Company and our affiliates by simply sending such a request to us at the numbers or addresses given below.  Once you opt-out, we will honor your choice until you inform us otherwise.

#### WHO CAN YOU CONTACT FOR MORE INFORMATION?

**Data Protection Authority**  
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) and believe we maintain your personal data subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to your local supervisory authority or our lead supervisory authority, the UK’s Information Commissioner’s Office, as noted below:  
Information Commissioner’s Office  
Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, United Kingdom  
Phone: 0303 123 1113

**Contact us**  
If you have any privacy-related questions, concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy, our practices or our Services, you may contact our Office of the DPO by email at [privacy@godaddy.com](mailto:privacy@godaddy.com).

In the alternative, you may contact us by either of the following means:  
• By Mail:  
Attn: Office of the Data Protection Officer, 14455 North Hayden Road, Suite 219, Scottsdale, AZ 85260 USA,  
or for customers established in the EEA,  
Attn: Legal, Office of the DPO, 5th Floor, The Shipping Building, Old Vinyl Factory, 252-254 Blyth Road, Hayes, UB3 1HA, UK.

• By Phone:  
US DPO office: (480) 505-8877.

**YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND AND CONSENT TO THE PRIVACY PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF USE REFERENCED HEREIN**.

_Last revised: Aug 27, 2019_
